What are consumables benefits in health insurance
and should you
take this policy or not, we will
talk about it before starting the video I would
like to say yes to you
my name is Ibn Tahir and I am Sakshi
Shukla, I bring a lot of
videos from home so that your
personality can become easy and better
because our front leg is
creating awareness of peanut let's move
towards the video in this video we
will talk about what are consumables
but what does consumables
mean in it what are the non to have no
items and should you take this consumables
ideal or not or should you
take that policy which has it inbuilt, we will
talk about this first let's understand if the
gym is closed tomorrow consumables are usually those
things which are used after use it is
medical aid or
equipment it means one time this is
what you can say and what is this
tomorrow if you have a bill for the gym or for the criminal
you will have to serve  5 are postponed, then there is something
special in it, so you see that it is
not covered by the insurance company, what is that, that is a non-
tribal item,
we will discuss about that country pump today in 2016, IRDA which is the
insurance regulator, they have prepared a
list of non
-tribal items, there are 199 items which are listed in your policy, so this is the main thing and you can check all the health insurance policies for this, in your body building there is a column for non-tribal items, it is at the
last, you can see
what things are not listed and this diary
is billed to you and if there is
no applicant to pay it, then there is
curvature in it, if we
talk about administrative service on the force, then for
admission date of birth certificate is required,
documentation explained, visit pass, if
someone comes then his express Delhi chart,
sources of procedure, medical record are all the
things which I am telling, you
can refer to the details here right now, housekeeping
items which include mineral water, toothpaste,
Rajesh  Pass science paper, Kunar
shampoo powder, ad type and baby food carry
bags predictions in the room ask for
low light on Panchami like telephone charges,
televisions, DVD players, conditioners, attendants,
Rajdhaat strike, we will talk about surgical items
when we are
undergoing surgery, those scientific items are used
in every country, that is, their
purpose is non-medical expenses like
cotton, razor, needle, Screen Actors Guild
of America gown, net, the most common is
four drops of papaya which we saw in all,
due to which we came to know that consumer Bill
Cosby is that terrorism in which
you saw Tabla Sand last year and
in the last friends, according to the quality, there are
many companies which do not pay for tempered glass
and also
clean the absorbent from the hospital, there also we came to know
that some such companies do not have to pay for state health insurance
companies, let me
tell you just a few things, there are 300 items and towel
line, yes you can check the detailed list
in your policy building, these items are there
in your policy  10,000
points travel items non medical expenses are not covered
why are we talking about it today we are talking about it
because earlier it used to be
that your 256 percent paas
hoti because of consumables suppose if a
bill of 1 lakh came then 2 to 5000 maximum and
in search of higher side but what is the thing
that non medical expenses and travel items are
usual but quite what happened after that that
point increased
from 10 to 15 percent means where it was found in
2008 it started making 15 percent
because things will start getting used more so that is why we
saw from those insurance companies that it is
necessary to report on the highest items they have developed into
major part that means big bills if
you have long hospitalization means
understand that someone stays in hospital for a long time
10 days 15 days then its officer said that
Big Boss will go for a lot so that is why
we saw that there is this gap so to
cover this more riders are there
Many policy revisions have been brought in which consumer
investment is a huge cost, there is news of many polythene
grids and they will bring here that you should get additional
cream, see you can get it withdrawn tomorrow morning,
we will meet again, you do
not need to pay, then your policy becomes a fully covered
policy, like riders do, and till
we talk about gym tomorrow, then
the decision making here is not of the policy holder,
not of the patient, or
why most of the time it is the doctor's decision, for example,
if you want to use a cotton swab
or cotton fringes, then
which quality should you use,
transferable, 500ml,
and secondly, if you have a cloth open
for you, secondly, if there is any
remaining cloth left in it, then it is best for you,
you will be charged on your entire face, so you do
not have any depression meeting about what to use,
how much to use and which quality to
use, diet decision making life with the
hospital Angry Birds playlist, so
therefore, be patient and it is
important to cover Assange's consumables, that  The
job he did, so when we
talk about the rider, the premium of health
insurance is 5.5 to 10%,
this is special on Basant Panchami, so when we talk about
10,000 Wicket Inch Plus Cream, then
your cost will be from 7.5 years to thousands of rupees, the rider is
national money, see, we have included that,
consumer loan, table items will be covered
in the policy, so whatever bill comes tomorrow, that
insurance, if we get out of the possibility of the
incident, then there is definitely a pension for you
because Ko Stop Tanu members in total will have increased
their feeling passenger, so if
that cost has increased, then look at it a little here, it is
better to cover it, rub it a lot, so
it is wise that you
take the rider, at least till we feel that
Ko Beeds or till we feel that
this robot will be more expensive in Punjab, then
whatever policy you are going to take for 101 years, then if you have
this tank and then you can add it,
later you can see
where to remove it.  In English, you can remove it anytime or
add it anytime, that is
your choice, so on one hand, we solve
any questions about consumables, non-tribals, lighters,
this recording or health insurance
in general regarding this, then
please talk to us on our WhatsApp number of Kayan Tower, you
can also tell us in the comment section, a reminder, if
you have not yet subscribed to our channel, do
subscribe, get
desired information and a lifetime like
I have said and we will meet you
in the next video, just take care by,
thank you
[Music]
MP3 It has happened that
in 2016, the festival is that, that
dena, now
jhalar kar do kar do, it has
happened, kar do
jhal